supercheats.com 2019-09-20

# Super Cheats - Privacy Policy

Last Updated May 24th 2018

**Important Notice**

SuperCheats.com started life in 1999 as a website aimed at helping people get the most out of their games. Over the lifetime of our website we have remained a free to access reource, accessed by millions of people around the world, with advertising being our only revenue stream. We can only remain online if people continue to allow us to serve advertsing alongside our content.

We take your privacy seriously, and are committed to your privacy and protection of your personal information, we hope these values are transmitted correctly in our privacy policy.

**Summary – Policy Overview**

This Policy explains how we may Process your information. This Policy may be amended or updated from time to time, so please check it regularly for updates.

Web Media Network Limited owns and operates several interactive websites, including SuperCheats.com. This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected about you by Web Media Network, regardless of how it is collected or stored, and describes, among other things, the types of information collected about you when you interact with our websites and/or apps, how your information may be used, when your information may be disclosed, how you can control the use and disclosure of your information, and how your information is protected.

Our privacy policy may be updated from time to time, and we encourage you to check back regularly to review any changes that may be made.

This Privacy Policy covers information collected through the following websites:

[https://supercheats.com](https://www.supercheats.com/) (including all sub-domains)

**What Information We May Process**

When registering a free account on our website we will ask you for your email address, and your date of birth (to check that no-one under 13 registers). We offer interactions on our sites in the form of comments, forum posts, questions and answers, and other views and opinions, once submitted they will be recorded on our website as interactions by you under your account name on our website.

You can at any time request for your account to be deleted and/or have the information you have submitted under your account name deleted at any time. Please do this via our contacts form.

As a security measure we also log the IP address that you access our website from, this data allows us to monitor site activity and check that our service is not being abused, and ban IP addresses from accessing our service.

We may also process information about you from your use of our services (e.g., the type of device you are using, the internet service provider, etc.), including your interactions with content and advertising on the services.

We may process the following categories of Personal Information about you:

Personal details: username; password; email address; date of birth; ip address

Consent records: records of any consents you may have given, together with the date and time, means of consent and any related information

Statistical information: We use Google Analytics to provide us with aggregated statistical data based on our website visitors, this is non-personally identiable information.

We also collect other kinds of information from you or other sources, which we refer to as “Other Information” in this Policy, which may include but is not limited to:

Information about your use of the Services, such as usage data and statistical information, which may be aggregated.

Browsing history including the websites or other services you visited before and after interacting with the Services.

Information collected through the use of cookies, eTags, Javascript, pixel tags, device ID tracking, anonymous identifiers and other technologies, including information collected using such methods and technologies about (i) your visits to, and interaction and engagement with, the Services, content and ads on third party websites, applications, platforms and other media channels (“Channels”), and (ii) your interaction with emails including the content and ads therein (collectively, “Online Data”).

Log files, which may include IP addresses, browser type, ISP referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamps.

Web Beacons, which are electronic files that allow a website to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies.

Pixel Tags, also known as clear GIFs, beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, which are a method for passing information from the user’s computer to a third party website.

Local Shared Objects, such as Flash cookies, and Local Storage, such as HTML5.

**Sensitive Personal Information**

We do not seek to collect or otherwise Process your Sensitive Personal Information. For example this may include your phone number, home address, employer details, religous views etc...

**Use of our Services by Children**

The Services are not intended for use by unaccompanied children, especially those under 13, as our website contains comments from the public which may be inappropriate for children to read. While we do our best to moderate inappropriate commnents, due to the real-time nature of commenting some may appear before we have a chance to moderate and some may appear if we make a mistake in moderating comments and other posts. No one under the age of 13 should provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums or chats. Any child wanting to browse our website should do so with a responsible adult, such as a parent or guardian that will be able to make decisions on privacy and cookie consent. If you believe that a child under 13 has registered on our website please let us know at webmaster@supercheats.com.

**Email a friend and share this article facilities**

When you use these facilities and provide us with personal data (for example, name and email address) of a third party, please ensure that you have their consent before giving us their details.

**Purposes for Which We May Process Your Information**

We process your information to help us provide our a functioning, interactive website service to you, to communicate with you and to provide advertising to you on our website. We also use aggregated statistical information which is non-personally identifibable to provide us with statistical data about our website and it's visitors, such as how many pages they usually view, what countries our audience is from, which pages are the most popular etc...

**Will I get SPAM from you?**

We do not participate in SPAM, selling email addresses, or even sending out regular marketing or infomational emails. Generally the only emails you can expect from us would be a response after you initially making contact with us by email or via a contact form, or notification about a data update based on an opted-in setting such as notification that yourr question has been answered, or notification that a guide has been updated (you would have to exlicitly opt-in on each individual guide). You can manage the notifications that you receive from us by visting: https://www.supercheats.com/myaccount/accountsettings while being logged in with your registered account.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of information that is placed on your computer when you visit certain websites. When we refer to 'cookies' we include other technologies with similar purposes.

We use the following types of cookie:

1) Cookies for website function (essential cookies)

These cookies allow us to offer a website which functions as intended, we use this information to track whether or not you are logged in and allow our website to respond accordingly. You can block cookies via your browser settings, however all browsers are different and the exact instructions are different for each browser.

Also, if youy decide to block our website cookies we cannot guarantee the expected user experience and our website may not function as intended.

Here are some instructions for cookie management in some popular browsers:

Chrome

[https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en)

Safari

<https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411?locale=en_GB>

Internet Explorer

<https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>

The links above are all on external sites, therefore we have no idea if that content changes over time or becomes outdated and cannot be held responsible for usage of the data on those pages.

2) Third-Party Cookies for statistical tracking

These cookies track the pages you visit, and give us things such as non-personally identificable information about the country to state you are visiting our site from, what browser you are using and from what device and other. The tracking cookie that we use is Google Analytics. For more information about Google Analytics and how the safeguard and use your data please see this link: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en-GB>

If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics, Google have provided a borwser plug in which you can find out about here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB>

3) Third Party Cookies for advertising and marketing

These cookies allow us to help us serve the correct advertising to you when you visit our website. They are placed by or on behalf of independent advertisers who are advertising on our site. These cookies may be placed within the advertisement and elsewhere on our site. They are anonymous – they cannot identify individuals. They might also allow the advertiser to customise advertising to you when you visit other websites. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://youronlinechoices.com/>

If you deny us consent to use cookies on your device then you will still be able to access our website but it may limit us in terms of what service we can offer to you now and in the future.

For example if you do not consent to advertising cookies, then the simple fact is that our revenue will be impacted and at some point we may not be able to operate this site in the basis we do now. We provide our website on the assumption that it is consumed alongside the advertising in exchange for accessing our content without a monetary fee.

We have no access to third party cookies and third party organisations have no access to ours. The third party organisations that place cookies have their own strict privacy policies.

**Protecting your information**

The password you provide when registering with the website is encrypted to ensure protection against unauthorised access to your personal information. Our servers which store the data you have submitted to us are kept up to date with the relevant security patches in a timely manner as they become available. However, no data transmission over the Internet or the storage of such data can be entirely secure, and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and/or use of the website. Any information that you send is at your own risk and may be read by others.

**Disclosing your information**

We may disclose your personal information to third parties and their advisers if we are approached by a potential buyer in connection with the potential sale of our business, or of any part of it. Should we proceed to sell any part of our business that holds your personal information, it will be necessary in some circumstances to share or transfer that information to the buyer or new entity.

We may disclose your personal information if we believe are legally obliged to do so.

We never sell personal information, or pass it to third parties (except subject to legal requirements) for their own marketing purposes, without your permission.

**Where we store your personal information**

The personal information that we collect from you may be sent and stored outside the European Economic Area ("EEA").

**Access to your Information**

You can access your information by logging into your account. It is possible to request to change the email address associated with your account in your account settings. If you would like to delete, your account or data in in, please get in touch with us at [webmaster@supercheats.com](mailto:webmaster@supercheats.com).

**Getting in Touch, and Privacy Concerns**

If you have any concerns about the way we handle your personal data, would like to make changes to the data that we hold on you, delete your account and all of your data, please get in touch with us at [webmaster@supercheats.com](mailto:webmaster@supercheats.com)
